<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Zangwei</title>
    <link>https://zhengzangw.com/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Zangwei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>zhengzangw@gmail.com (Zangwei (Alex) Zheng)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>zhengzangw@gmail.com (Zangwei (Alex) Zheng)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:43:38 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zhengzangw.com/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://zhengzangw.com/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 02:47:43 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>zhengzangw@gmail.com (Zangwei (Alex) Zheng)</author>
      <guid>https://zhengzangw.com/about/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Ph.D. student at National University of Singapore, advised by Prof. Yang You. I received my B.Sc. in Computer Science from Nanjing University in 2021. I spent one year in iCyPy at UC Berkeley from Apr. 2020, supervised by Prof. Alberto L. Sangiovanni-Vincentelli and Dr. Xiangyu Yue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Interest</title>
      <link>https://zhengzangw.com/about/interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 02:47:43 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>zhengzangw@gmail.com (Zangwei (Alex) Zheng)</author>
      <guid>https://zhengzangw.com/about/interest/</guid>
      <description>My current research mainly focus on Video Generation, Efficient ML (machine learning) and Large-scale DL (Deep Learning) Optimization.
Video Generation: large-scale video generation model, video control and alignment. Large-scale DL Optimization: optimizer design (faster, memory-efficient, robust, etc.), optimizer explanation, data-model-algorithm connections. Efficient ML: computation-efficient training (accelerated optimizer, large batch training, incremental learning), memory-efficient training, efficient inference. I am always happy to chat about interesting research ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://zhengzangw.com/about/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 02:47:43 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>zhengzangw@gmail.com (Zangwei (Alex) Zheng)</author>
      <guid>https://zhengzangw.com/about/news/</guid>
      <description>[2025.3] Open-Sora 2.0 released! Despite limited compute, it achieves Sora-level metrics and fulfills our initial vision of providing an open-source Sora implementation 🚀 [2024.9] Got one paper (MSIER) accepted to EMNLP 2024. Congratulations to Yang Luo! [2024.9] VideoOcean is now online! Generate your own video with a few clicks. [2024.6] Got one paper (Dataset Growth) accepted to ECCV 2024. Congratulations to Ziheng Qin! [2024.6] Open-Sora 1.2 released! A 1.1B models on &amp;gt;30M data with improved performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://zhengzangw.com/about/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:33:19 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>zhengzangw@gmail.com (Zangwei (Alex) Zheng)</author>
      <guid>https://zhengzangw.com/about/publications/</guid>
      <description>See Google Scholar for the most up-to-date list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Assistant</title>
      <link>https://zhengzangw.com/about/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:31:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>zhengzangw@gmail.com (Zangwei (Alex) Zheng)</author>
      <guid>https://zhengzangw.com/about/teaching/</guid>
      <description> CS 5242: Neural Networks and Deep Learning (NUS, Fall 2022) Algorithm Analysis &amp;amp; Design (NJU, Fall 2020) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Awards</title>
      <link>https://zhengzangw.com/about/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:43:38 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>zhengzangw@gmail.com (Zangwei (Alex) Zheng)</author>
      <guid>https://zhengzangw.com/about/awards/</guid>
      <description> 2023, Research Achievement Award of NUS 2023, ACL 2023 Outstanding Paper Award 2023, AAAI 2023 Distinguished Paper Award 2022, Papers with Code Contributor Award 2021, Outstanding Graduates of Nanjing University 2020, Outstanding Student of Nanjing University 2019, 2018 (2 times), National Elite Program First-Class Scholarship 2019, Zheng Gang Overseas Study Scholarship </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://zhengzangw.com/about/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:40:24 +0800</pubDate>
      <author>zhengzangw@gmail.com (Zangwei (Alex) Zheng)</author>
      <guid>https://zhengzangw.com/about/projects/</guid>
      <description> Open-Sora: Open-source video generation model. ColossalChat: A chatbot developed with ColossalAI. Instruction in the Wild: 110K high-quailty user-based instructions. awesome-huge-models: Collection of huge AI models. hugo-theme-phd: Hugo theme for this page. Overview of the Evolution of the Universe and Related Disciplines </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
